bestjobaroundtheworld.com 2015-06-26

# Jauntaroo | Your Vacation Matchmaker

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when becoming a registered member, subscribing to communications, responding to surveys, filling out forms or aggregating non-identifiable data with cookies during general site use.

Personally identifiable information provided during the registration process will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

When [registering](http://www.jauntaroo.com/users/signup) on our site you will be asked to enter: your name, e-mail address, zip code and other demographic information used to personalize your experience.

You may also visit our site anonymously.

### How do we use your information?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  * To improve our website: we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  * To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your requests, needs and/or feedback
  * To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested
  * To administer promotions, campaigns, surveys or other site features
  * To send periodic emails: The email address you provide and confirm upon registration, may be used to send you occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We do not store private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s Web browser, if you allow, that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business as well as personalize advertisements.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve customized ads to our visitors based on visits to our site and other internet sites as well as measure our web traffic and available interest-based audience data. Third-party vendors, including Google, also use first-party and third-party cookies together to report ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. Using Google’s ad settings, visitors can opt-out of their display advertising by visiting [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCijX_Y5iNgASd-rHA_eneeWE7CWGWZ4TGbzJh6y6-1AMGu9MJNSpkd9N2zMDgnP3JXVRToIlAdCZazwjg23QhJD5l0U8bGTT6ZccPMAzzwbpK37Xp_LQQh8F285Wa8zm7tiHEADujU3GlKxEdLthPUhkj5JAc-PqDNKAQO-agP6m2s4BCdWGs2uHYzMa9SD2fF7ovaQa2VQkSQkHd3ET1N33mW5hw). Additional available Google opt-outs for the web can be viewed [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still use the site.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their account.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.jauntaroo.com/pages/terms-and-conditions>

### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy at <http://www.jauntaroo.com/pages/privacy-policy>

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

When changes to our privacy policy are made, we will update the following Privacy Policy modification date:

This policy was last modified on December 6, 2013.

### Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

P.O. Box 451  
Smithfield, UT 84335  
United States  

© 2011-2014 Vacation Travel Match, LLC, All Rights Reserved.

Jauntaroo®, “Your Vacation Matchmaker”™ are registered trademarks of Vacation Travel Match.
